Tomasz Michal Klosinski

16 Avenue du Jura 01210 Ferney-Voltaire France

+33 755 77 37 37

tomasz.klosinski@protonmail.ch PGP: E75959Bo

linkedin.com/in/tklosinski

We do not act rightly because we have virtue or excellence, but we rather have those because we have acted rightly. We are what we repeatedly do.

Excellence, then, is not an act but a habit.

—Aristotle, Nichomachean Ethics

I am B.A. graduate of Computer Science and B.A. graduate of Business Management, both held in English, at University of Lodz, and M.A. graduate of IT (Databases) at Polish-Japanese Academy of Information Technology. I have been working in Linux world for last 4 years and I have been passionate Linux user for over 13 years. My current position is System Engineer for DevOps and Infrastructure teams at CERN Control Center.

Areas of Interest

DevOps, Continuous Delivery Cloud Computing, IT Infrastructure Management, Agile Methodologies LANGUAGES

Polish (Native proficiency)
English (Full professional proficiency)
French (Limited professional proficiency)

Previous Experience

2015–2016 CERN, *Project Associate* Geneva

At CERN Control Center I have been working in support team of over 2000 (OpenStack) VMs, desktops and servers (60% real-time kernel). Most of the servers that I have been taking care of were Linux machines providing the mission critical software for the operation of LHC and other accelerators. Along with my daily support and troubleshooting tasks, I have been involved in numerous activities in System Administration Modernisation project.

2014—2015 Linux Polska, Solution Architect Warsaw

At Linux Polska I have worked on a continuous delivery system for building rpm packages. I have contributed also to the organization of the biggest Open Source event in Poland (which Linux Polska is co-organizing every year in May): Open Source Day.

2011–2014 IMPAQ, Software / System Engineer Warsaw

My career as a System Engineer at IMPAQ can be split into two periods. For first half year I have been member of a support team of RHEL-based telco applications for international cellular networks. For another 1.5+ year I have worked for Machine-to-Machine, Cloud Computing and Big Data Business Practice (Department).

2010–2011 Оитвох, Junior Consultant Warsaw

At Outbox I have worked on the development of the CRM system based on Oracle PeopleSoft platform for Telekomunikacja Polska SA.

Education

2010-2012

Polish-Japanese Academy of Information Technology

Databases, M.A. Warsaw

2008–2011 University of Lodz

Business Management, B.A.

Lodz

2007–2010
University of Lodz
Computer Science, B.A.

Cerification

Red Hat Certified Engineer (2014–2017) Red Hat Certified System Administrator (2014–2017)

Skills

Linux, Bash Ansible, Python, Vagrant, Chef, Ruby, Jenkins Elasticsearch, Logstash, Kibana MySQL, PostgreSQL Apache HTTPD, nginx, HAProxy Nagios, Zabbix

Projects

2010–2012 Polish-Japanese Academy of Information Technology **Databases**, M.A. Warsaw

2008–2011 University of Lodz Business Management, B.A. Lodz

2007–2010 University of Lodz Computer Science, B.A. Lodz